onobello.com 2013-12-19

# OnoBello.com Privacy Policy Statement - OnoBello.com: Latest in Fashion, Beauty, News, Features and Events

**1\. General**

This policy covers OnoBello.com, a site produced by PR UNO Limited. PR UNO Limited is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you what personal information PR UNO Limited collects and the purposes for which it uses this information. This policy may change from time to time so please check back here periodically. In reviewing this privacy policy, please read our Website terms and conditions.

**2\. Disclosures**

PR UNO Limited may disclose your information, under strict terms of confidentiality and restriction of use, to partners of PR UNO Limited who supply services on behalf of PR UNO Limited and who need to process personal data in the provision of such services. When you use OnoBello.com you are consenting to the disclosure of your personal information to PR UNO Limited partners. PR UNO Limited will not disclose any of your personal information to any other third parties without your express consent. However, under certain circumstances the force of law may require the provision of information to legal authorities. In order to maintain the integrity of its website and safeguard the interests of its subscribers OnoBello.com will comply with any such legally binding request.

**3\. Information Collected**

3.1.      Identifiable information - Your information is collected when you register or fill in a form on OnoBello.com, or you send an email to OnoBello.com. The information that is provided by you will only be used for the purpose for which it is provided, unless you are informed otherwise at the time of giving the information. You may inform PR UNO Limited at any time if you wish PR UNO Limited to cease using your personal information.

3.2.      Non identifiable information - PR UNO Limited will from time to time collect information from you that does not reveal your personal identity. PR UNO Limited uses this information for editorial purposes, and occasionally for other internal purposes. This information is only used in aggregate form and is not connected to any name, address or other personal identifying information.

**4\. Use of personal information**

PR UNO Limited processes personal information for the purpose of providing a personalised service, conducting market research surveys, running competitions and providing you with information about products and services on offer. PR UNO Limited may from time to time use your contact information to tell you about news or events provided by PR UNO Limited or one of its strategic partners. You may opt-out of receiving such mailings, either when you register with OnoBello.com or at any time afterwards. PR UNO Limited may also contact you with important information about your registration details even if you have opted-out of receiving promotional emails.

**5\. Use of Cookies**

Cookies are small amounts of information that are sent to and are stored on your computer. They are used to identify you when you visit the site, and to make your use of the site more convenient for you. Cookies are used to remember usernames, passwords and preferences and to deliver a faster and more personalised service.

The OnoBello.com site and service may contain advertisements created and provided by a third party. These advertisements may place Cookies on your computer that collect information about you and your use of the Internet. PR UNO Limited does not control the collection or use of your information by such advertisers and this privacy policy does not apply to such information.

If you do not wish to have Cookies placed on your computer you can disable Cookies on your Internet browser. Turning them off however will mean that you will not be able to enjoy the OnoBello.com website to the fullest.

**6\. Links**

There are links on OnoBello.com to third party web sites which PR UNO Limited has no control over. PR UNO Limited accepts no responsibility or liability for any third party practices on third party websites. PR UNO Limited advises you to carefully read 3rd party privacy statements prior to the use of any third party website.

**7\. International Transfers**

Due to the international nature of the Internet, the collecting and processing of your personal information in accordance with PR UNO Limited privacy policy will often involve transferring the data between countries in which PR UNO Limited, other companies in the PR UNO Limited group of companies and strategic partners are located.

PR UNO Limited shall take steps to ensure that any transfer of data to a country or territory outside the European Economic Area, whose laws provide for a different standard of protection for your personal data than that provided under English law, shall be made subject to contractual arrangements which will require that your data be processed to at least a standard compliant with the Data Protection Act in Nigeria.

**8\. Security**

This Website has security measures in place to protect against loss, misuse and alteration of your personal information under PR UNO Limited control. However no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and whilst PR UNO Limited strives to protect your personal information, PR UNO Limited cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once PR UNO Limited receives the transmission, PR UNO Limited makes best efforts to ensure the security on the system.

**9\. Contact Details**

**Email:**[](mailto:%3Ca%20href=) [ ](mailto:%3Ca%20href=)[style.director@onobello.com](mailto:style.director@onobello.com)

**Mobile:** +234 (0) 705 810 738

**CHILDREN AND PARENTS**

OnoBello.com is not intended for use by children, especially those under age 12. No one under age 12 is allowed to provide any personal information or use our public discussion areas, forums and chats. Minors between the ages of 12 and 17 must get the permission of their parent(s) or legal guardian(s) before making purchases, including subscriptions, on this site.

If your children disclose information about themselves in our public discussion areas, they may get unsolicited messages from other parties. Accordingly, you should tell them not to do so.

If you're worried about your children's activities or their privacy on our site, we encourage you to e-mail our Founder/Style Director at [](mailto:%3Ca%20href=)[ ](mailto:%3Ca%20href=)[style.director@onobello.com](mailto:style.director@onobello.com)

If you have other concerns or questions about any aspect of this policy, you may also e-mail our Founder/Style Director at [style.director@onobello.com](mailto:style.director@onobello.com). We welcome your feedback.

**COMPETITIONS**

Entrants must be at least 18 years of age and proof of age will be required before the prize is dispatched.

All qualifying entrants who answer the question correctly will be placed in a free prize draw.

Winners will be notified within 28 days of the draw taking place.

There is no cash alternative to the prize.

This competition is run by PR UNO Limited, and is connected with OnoBello.com.

The competition is not open to anyone associated with PR UNO Limited and OnoBello.com.

The judges' decision is final and no correspondence will be entered into.

A list of winners' names is available on written request to: [](mailto:%3Ca%20href=)[ ](mailto:%3Ca%20href=)[style.director@onobello.com](mailto:style.director@onobello.com).

No responsibility can be accepted for entries which are not properly received due to communications beyond our control.
